[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
We've done now some simple regression, some simple regression for
我们已经做了一些简单的回归
our data just using square foot of living.
只关于我们数据的居住面积的一些基础的回归
But if you remember, our data set had many other columns associated with that, or
但 如果你记得的话 我们的数据集还有其他与之相关的列
features.
可以试着给你一点点直观的参考
So what we're gonna do next is
所以我们下一步要做的是
explore other features in the data.
#挖掘数据里的其他特征
So let's do some exploration of other possible features we might use.
所以我们来探索其他我们可能用到的特征
So I'm going to use a set of features.
我们将用到一系列的特性
So let's create a list of the features I'm going to explore, the code features.
所以 我们把各种特征列出来 我将探索它的编码特征
And these features are going to be the number
这些特征是
of bedrooms, the number of bathrooms.
卧室和浴室的数量
Let's see, what else?
让我们想想 还有啥？
The square foot of living space, which is what we've been exploring so far.
还有居住空间的面积 这是我们到现在一直在研究的
In addition to this, I'm going to include the square foot of the lot, so
除了这些 还要包括建筑用地的面积
this is how much land the house has all around it.
这是属于这栋建筑的周围的面积
The number of floors in the house.
房屋的层数
And finally, I'm gonna include a variable called the ZIP code.
最后 我还囊括了一个变量叫做ZIP code
And so the ZIP code in
Zip code就是
the United States is what other countries call the postal code.
其他国家的邮编在美国的叫法
In Brazil we call this SAPI.
巴西叫它 SAPI
But there are many names in different places, that's what we'll include.
这个在不同的地方有不同的叫法 这就是我们引入的这个特征
So, let's see, if I take the sales data and I just select this column,
如果我看着这个Sales 这个数据 然后我选择其中某一列
just select the features column here, why don't we call them just to be totally
选择特征列  让我们表达的更清晰些吧
clear, instead of calling them features I'm going to call them my_features.
与其叫特征(features) 不如叫我的特征(my_features)
Shift+Enter.
重新运行一下 按shift+回车
And then I'm gonna look at what my_features columns look like.
这样这就是我my_features 列
So I'm gonna type .show.
然后我输入sales[my_feature].show()来打印出结果
Remember, we can type .show anything with GraphLab Create.
记住了 我们可以用show这个指令来打印任何GraphLab 创造出来的东西
On the sframe for sales, selecting the my_features.
在Sales这个SFrame里面 选择my_features这些列
And now we're gonna have a visualization of these features.
然后对这些特征进行一个可视化
So let me just walk you through this visualization.
让我带你看一下可视化的结果
Get my mouse here.
把鼠标移动到这
So bedrooms, let's look at frequency.
看到卧室的数目
There are 13 different unique types.
有13种不同的类型
In fact, there's some houses with ten bedrooms.
事实上有些房子有着10间卧室
Most houses have three bedrooms.
大部分房子是三间卧室
Some have four, some have two, some have five, and very few have more.
有的四间 有的两间 有的五间 有很少一部分有更多的卧室数目
With bathrooms,
还带着卫生间的卧室
it turns out that house in the US, you have fractional number of bathrooms.
美国的房子 你有这着带着分数的卫生间数目
When you say, for example, 2.5 bathrooms is the most common number,
2.5间卧室是最常见的数目
it's because if you have a house with a bathroom with a bath in it,
这意味着 有的房子带着 自带卫生间的卧室
it's called a full bath, it counts for 1.
这个叫做完全卫生间 代表着1
But if you have just a bathroom that has a sink and a toilet, it's just worth 0.5.
如果有的卫生间只有一个水槽和马桶 这只能算半个
And so here you have 2.5.
所以说最后的数目是2.5个
In fact, if you have a bathroom with a sink, a toilet, and
如果你的卫生间 带着一个水槽 一个马桶 和淋浴的地方 但不包括浴缸 在美国这算0.75个
a shower, but no tub, that's worth 0.75 in the US.
但不包括浴缸 在美国这算0.75个
So there you go.
好了
That's where you can have one bathroom is the second most common, and
所以你会发现1个卫生间是第二常见的
then you have this 1.75 bathroom, which is probably
然后是1.75个
going to be one full bath with a bath and a bathroom with a shower.
也许意味着你会有一个完整的卫生间 和一个只有淋浴没有浴缸的卫生间
And you can see the distribution here.
同样你可以看到分布
Similarly for other things, like square foot of living, and
对于居住面积也是亦然
number of floors, most houses have one floor, some have two.
对于楼层来说 大部分房子是一层楼 有的是两层
And then the ZIP code.
然后就是邮编了
The most common zipcode is 98103,
最常见的是98103
which is an area where a lot of people live in Seattle.
也就是大部分住在西雅图的人的邮编
Okay, so
好的 那么
we've seen a high level visualization of the different columns of the data.
我们可以看到数据不同列的高度可视化的结果
Now let's look at some other relationships of the data.
让我们看看数据之间的关系吧
Let's do some fun visualizations here.
继续做一些有趣的可视化
So I'm gonna take the sales table and I'm gonna type show.
我还是会用到Sales这张表格 然后输入.show()
But the view that I'm gonna do, it's not gonna be scatterplot.
但是我不想看到散点图
But it's gonna be what is called a box whisker plot, and
所以在view这边我输入等于'BoxWhisker'
this box whisker plot is gonna relate two variables that we looked at.
BoxWhisker会给我们带来两个变量之间的关系
On the x side, I'm gonna use the ZIP code, so this is the postal code
在X轴我想要用zip code 也就是邮政编码
that we discussed, and on the y-axis, I'm going to plot the price.
在Y轴 我想用价格来表示
So what we're gonna see is the relationship between the location,
也就是 我们可以看到位置(邮编)
the ZIP code, where the house is, and the price.
和价格之间的关系
And we're gonna see that with what's called a box whisker plot.
所以这就是所谓的Box whisker 图了
So I'm gonna press Shift+Enter and we're gonna plot it.
然后按下Shift+回车 就能绘制出来
And here's what we'll see.
这就是我们所看到的
So you will see, for example,
举个例子
this area's zip code, post code,
这块区域的邮编
98003, has a significantly lower price.
98003 价格特别低
So the average price is low, that's the red line, and not a lot of variability.
平均价格是红色的线 而且这块区域价格没什么波动
While this other zip code 98004, so this is 003,
但是这一块98004 那个是003
98004, has a highest average price, much higher,
这个是004 有着最高的价格 比003 高多了
1 point something million, 1.1 million, and a huge variability.
100多万 而且有着巨大的上下限
So the houses range from something like, what is this?
所以说总共的范围是多少呢
$800,000, it's almost $4 million.
最低的大概在80万 最高的大概是400万
But here I'm just showing a few ZIP codes.
我仅仅显示了一些邮编地址
If I drag down here, you'll see more and more ZIP codes.
如果我往下拉你会看到更多的
And wow, what is this one over here?
有没有看到这个
There's one that's astronomical, it goes out of the scale.
这个价格都要突破天际了 超出范围了
Some houses here cost like, what is this?
谁家房子这么厉害
$7 million or something.
大概在700万的样子
And this post code is 98039.
邮编地址是98039
Remember 98039, we'll come back to it at the end of this notebook.
记住这个数字 我们在这节课最后会揭晓真相的
It's kind of funny.
这很有趣
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community